[{"answer": "Bullshit the thirtieth, I don't get on the board the thirtieth, they're going to can my ass.  I need the leads.  I need them now.  Or I'm gone, and you're going to miss me, my friend, I swear to you", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "...you talk to my friend..", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "...you talk to my friend..", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Marshal the leads...marshal the leads?  What the fuck, what bus did you get off of, we're here to fucking sell.  Fuck marshaling the leads.  What the fuck talk is that? What the fuck talk is that?  Where did you learn that?  In school?  That's", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Money.  A fortune.  Money lying on the ground.  my friend?  When was the last time he went out on a sit? Sales contest?  It's laughable. It's cold out there now, my friend. It's tight.  Money is tight.  This ain't sixt", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my friend.  my friend..", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "That's fucked.  That's fucked.  You don't look at the fucking percentage. You look at the gross", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I'm out", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Bullshit, bullshit, you assign them... What are you telling me", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What are we going to say", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I'm not sure I have two", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I'm not sure I have two", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " I've got that place.  Then I've got Moss..", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You missed a fucking sale.  Big deal.  A deadbeat Polack.  Big deal. How you going to sell 'em in the first place...?  Your mistake, you shoun'a took the lead", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You had to, yeah.  Why", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You had to, yeah.  Why", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "To get on the board.  Yeah.  How you goan'a get on the board sell'n a Polack?  And I'll tell you, I'll tell you what else.  You listening? I'll tell you what els", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well, I think I had one once", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I...I don't know", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "And now..", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "We're stuck with this fucking shit..", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "We're stuck with this..", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "...this shit..", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Starting up", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Of doing the thing.  The dif...the difference.  Between me and my friend.  Going to business for yourself.  The hard part is...you know what it is", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What act", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "That's what I..", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Men come work for you..", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "How many leads have we got", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "And you're saying a fella could take and sell these leads to my friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "my friend?  Because I worked for him", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No.  What do you mean?  Have I talked to him about this", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Yes.  I mean are you actually talking about this, or are we just..", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "We're just", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "No, we're just..", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "We're just speaking about it.  As an idea", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "We're just", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "As an idea", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "As a", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "No.  Not actually", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "What did you say", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Is that what I said", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "What did he say?  He'd buy them", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "You have to steal the leads tonight", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "They come to you, you going to turn me in", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "They're going to come to everyone", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Yes.  I'm sure", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Do you need five grand", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "You need money?  Is that the..", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Don't fuck with me, fella.  I'm talking about a fuckin' Cadillac car that you owe me..", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "They didn't get my contracts", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "They took some of the con..", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "You closed him yesterday", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Yeah.  That's swell.  Yes.  You're right.  How are you", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "I don't...yes.  Okay, the board", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "They're ancient", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Clear Meadows.  That shit's dead", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "He filed half of them, he filed the big one.  All the little ones, I have, I have to go back and...ah, fuck, I got to go out like a fucking schmuck hat in my hand and reclose the...  I mean, talk about a bad streak. That would sap anyone's self confi... I got to go out and reclose all my... Where's the phones", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "They stole the..", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Where criminals can come in here... they take the..", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "You think they're going to catch... where are you going", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "With what?  With what, my friend, they took the leads..", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Oh.  Oh.  Oh, your", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "Were the leads insured", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "'Cause, you know, 'cause they weren't, I know that my friend and my friend uh..", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "That's right.  You want to go out today...", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "A waste of time?  Why", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "Why don't you think so", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "Where were you", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "Why?  Because they're stupid.", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "Where was I", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "At home", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "Glad to meet you", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "No...Black Creek.  Yes.  In that place", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "Uh..", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "Home cooking..", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "Monday", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "Who did she call", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "Who did she call", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "Why did she do that, my friend", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "No, I'm saying you don't include Saturday...in your three days. It's not a business day", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "What would have elapsed", "qsentId": 90}, {"answer": "I want to work today, that's why I came..", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 93, "question": "...that's why I came in.  I thought I..", "qsentId": 92}, {"answer": "...that's why I came in.  I thought I..", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 95, "question": "I don't want to go to lunch", "qsentId": 94}, {"answer": "Just go to lunch", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 97, "question": "Go to lunch, my friend", "qsentId": 96}, {"answer": " What is", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 99, "question": "Tell me again", "qsentId": 98}, {"answer": "What's going on here", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 101, "question": "I told you", "qsentId": 100}, {"answer": "Tell me again.  Your wife", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 103, "question": "You tell me again", "qsentId": 102}, {"answer": "She told me if not, I have to call the State's attorney", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 105, "question": "She told me I have to", "qsentId": 104}, {"answer": "I don't have the power.  I said it", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 107, "question": "The power to negotiate", "qsentId": 106}, {"answer": "You are", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 109, "question": "What are you trying to tell me", "qsentId": 108}, {"answer": "I told the customer that his contracts had gone to the bank", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 111, "question": "No.  It hadn't", "qsentId": 110}, {"answer": "How much did you get for them?  How much did you get for them", "docId": "Glengarry-Glen-Gross.txt", "asentId": 113, "question": "Who kept the other half", "qsentId": 112}]